{
	"testi1": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Which town is Finland's capital?",
				"answer": "B",
				"options": "A:Ylivieska B:Helsinki C:Kouvola D:Toejoki"
			},
			{
				"question": "How many people live in Finland?",
				"answer": "D",
				"options": "A:Five B:50 C:500 D:5000000"
			},
			{
				"question": "How tall is Turku castle?",
				"answer": "B",
				"options": "A:10km B:100m C:200m D:1000m"
			},
			{
				"question": "What is capital of Varsinais-Suomi?",
				"answer": "C",
				"options": "A:Salo B:Raisio C:Turku D:Naantali"
			},
			{
				"question": "When was Turku cathedral built?",
				"answer": "B",
				"options": "A:1100's B:1200's C:1300's D:1400's"
			},
			{
				"question": "When was handcraft museum in Luostarinmäki founded? ",
				"answer": "D",
				"options": "A:1930 B:1934 C:1938 D:1940"
			}
		]
	},
	"testi2": {
		"questions": [
			{
				"question": "Which town is Finland's capital?",
				"answer": "B",
				"options": "A:Ylivieska B:Helsinki C:Kouvola D:Toejoki"
			},
			{
				"question": "How many people live in Finland?",
				"answer": "D",
				"options": "A:Five B:50 C:500 D:5000000"
			},
			{
				"question": "How tall is Turku castle?",
				"answer": "B",
				"options": "A:10km B:100m C:200m D:1000m"
			},
			{
				"question": "What is capital of Varsinais-Suomi?",
				"answer": "C",
				"options": "A:Salo B:Raisio C:Turku D:Naantali"
			},
			{
				"question": "When was Turku cathedral built?",
				"answer": "B",
				"options": "A:1100's B:1200's C:1300's D:1400's"
			},
			{
				"question": "When was handcraft museum in Luostarinmäki founded? ",
				"answer": "D",
				"options": "A:1930 B:1934 C:1938 D:1940"
			},
			{
				"question": "Who was the first president of Finland?",
				"answer": "C",
				"options": "A:Relander B:Kallio C:Ståhlberg D:Niinistö"
			},
			{
				"question": "When the winter war ended?",
				"answer": "A",
				"options": "A:13.3.1940 B:13.3.1939 C:13.3.1941 D:13.3.1942"
			},
			{
				"question": "What year Finland won their first hockey world championship?",
				"answer": "D",
				"options": "A:1988 B:1993 C:2011 D:1995"
			}
			
		]
	}
}